[{"question": "  hi.", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " hi, yeah, hi! i'm umm, phoebe buffay, and i have babies coming out of me.", "answer": " okay. have you started having contractions?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " not yet. umm, i heard they really hurt, do they hurt?", "answer": " well\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " oh my god!", "answer": " it's all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " oh no, none of them are the father. the father is my brother.", "answer": "  okay\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " i am so gonna miss watching you freak people out like that!", "answer": " okay, uh pheebs, quick. look! this  is for the babies to look at someday, so is-is there anything you want to say? y'know before it all starts?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " well, we-we had to go back because i forget my jacket.", "answer": " that's right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " you-you're not wearing a jacket.", "answer": " oh man! i did it again!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": "  okay, so umm, somebody has to call frank and alice.  and then my mom wants to know--joey, what are you doing?!", "answer": " i gotta get the before shot!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " hi, pheebs? okay, so just spoke to the nurse and the reason that your doctor is late is because uh, she's not coming.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " apparently she fell in the shower and hit her head.", "answer": " oh my god, she's so stupid!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " look, pheebs-pheebs, it's gonna be okay.", "answer": " that's easy for you to say, i don't see three kids coming out your vagina!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " honey, listen, y'know what? the nurse said the doctor is wonderful.", "answer": " yeah, he's head of the department.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " all right--ooh! oh dead god, save me!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " i'm having my first contraction!", "answer": " oh no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " ooh, it's not bad.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " hey! you okay?", "answer": " ooh, something hurts!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " ooh, it's sympathy pains. ohh, that's so sweet!", "answer": " are they? i didn't know i cared that much.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " hello.", "answer": " hi! phoebe, i'm dr. harad, i'm going to be delivering your babies. i want you to know, you're gonna be in good hands. i've been doing this for a long time. i'll be back in a minute to do your internal, in the meantime, just relax because everything here looks great. and also, i love fonzie.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " did he just say, he loves fonzie?", "answer": " that's what it sounded like.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " all right\u009a", "answer": "  hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": "  hey! am i late? am i late? nobody came out yet, right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " no-no-no! we haven't started yet. where's alice?", "answer": " uh, delaware. she's on her way though, so until she gets here, i'm gonna be your coach. but don't worry, she told me all about the la-mazada stuff.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " yeah, that's when if you get the babies out by the end of the month, they give you 2% financing.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": "  monica? you gonna be very proud of me. i just got us dates with two unbelievably cute nurses.", "answer": " oh my!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " they're male nurses.", "answer": " not in my head.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " anyway, they want to take us out saturday night! what do you say?", "answer": " umm.  umm. umm. i don't think so.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " what? what are you talking about?! you-you're the one who's been telling me to get over ross and move on. i'm moving on, and you're moving on with me. come on, give me one good reason why you don't wanna go.", "answer": " umm, why don't you give me something that would be a good reason and-and then i'll tell you if it's true.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " harder than it sounds. isn't it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " okay, you're coming with me, and i also told them that if we're still here when they get off that we'll go down to the cafeteria and have some jell-o with them.", "answer": "  yep! there's always room for jell-o\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " joey, how do you make that dirty?", "answer": " oh, it's easy. yeah, i-i can do it with anything. watch uh,  grandma's chicken salad\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " oh, okay, i'm having another one! this one doesn't hurt either--ooh, yes it does! ow! ow! ow! ow! ooh!  oh, i was kinda hoping that was it.", "answer": " hey, where are monica and rachel anyway?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " oh, a couple of nurses asked them out. maybe they're with them.", "answer": " really? male nurses?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " yeah, i was bummed too.", "answer": " so they're going on dates? when?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " i think saturday--.", "answer": "  what's with him?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " umm, sympathy pains. i thought it was really sweet at first, but now i think he's just trying to steal my thunder.", "answer": "  okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " let's see what we got here. ohh, y'know, fonzie dated triplets.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " this-this fonzie person you keep referring too, is that uh, is that another doctor?", "answer": " oh no-no-no. fonzie is the nickname of arthur fonzerelli. the fonz.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " it's not that weird, is it?", "answer": " it's very weird! i don't want some guy down there telling me, i'm y'know, dilatedamundo!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " to be fair, he doesn\u0092t seem to be impersonating fonzie\u009a", "answer": "  what are you doing?!! why are you defending him?! just get me another doctor! one who is not crazy and who is not fonzie!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": "  oh-hey-hey-hey! there you are!", "answer": " umm, listen there's something i think you should know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " oh, is this about you-you dating the nurse? yeah, joey already told me, and i am so-so fine. i mean, you and i we're just, y'know, we're nothing, we're goofin' around.", "answer": " umm, actually i was about to tell you that i was, i was going to get out of it, but hey, if we're just goofing around then uh, maybe i will go out with him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " fine! maybe i will too!", "answer": "  hey, you guys! look what i found in the giiiiiiift shop.  get up! get up! get up!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " okay, phoebe, this dr. oberman. he has no strong feelings about fonzie or any of the happy days gang.", "answer": " hi! and you're going into what grade?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " umm, i'm actually a first year resident, but i get that a lot, you see, i-i graduated early\u009a", "answer": "  uh-huh, me too. ross, maybe i should've specified that i'd be needing a grown up doctor.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " oh no, i'm fully qualified to\u009a", "answer": " shh! doogie, shh! doesn't anybody understand that i'm gonna be having babies soon? huh? go! go little boy, go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " mr. tribbiani, i'm afraid you've got kidney stones.", "answer": " umm, well, what else could it be?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " it's kidney stones.", "answer": " or?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " all right, you're getting there. oh, and y'know, these babies are very, very lucky.", "answer": " they are. why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " they have the honor of being born on the fonz's half-birthday.", "answer": " happy birthday!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " honey, y'know i just gotta tell you, i think this is such a terrific thing you're having these babies for frank and alice.", "answer": " i know, it is.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " yeah!", "answer": " can i tell you a little secret?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " yeah!", "answer": " i want to keep one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " okay, phoebe, honey, you gotta be kidding. i mean, you know you cannot keep one of these babies!", "answer": " why not?! maybe i can, you don't know!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " yes! yes! yes, i do! i do know! frank and alice are gonna want to keep all of their children!", "answer": " maybe not! y'know? seriously, three babies are a handful maybe they're y'know, looking for a chance to unload one of them. listen, i-i hate to miss an opportunity just because i didn't ask! y'know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " phoebe, no! this is, this is insane.", "answer": " oh, just ask him!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " me?!", "answer": " i can't ask him! do you have any idea how inappropriate that would be?! all i'm saying is just talk to frank. okay? just, y'know, feel him out!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " no! forget it! i am not gonna ask frank to give you one of his kids!!", "answer": " you're right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " feeling a little better sweetie?", "answer": " well, maybe a little. i wish you hadn't seen me throw up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " me too.", "answer": "  hey! i just heard. what's up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " kidney stones! now, ordinarily mr. tribbiani, we try to break up the stones up with shock waves, but they're to close to the bladder now. which means we can either wait for you to pass them or else go up the urethra\u009a", "answer": "  whoa-whoa! no-no-no-no-no, nothing is going up! okay? up, up is not an option--what's a urethra?  are you crazy?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": "  so did you ask him?", "answer": " no, i haven't had a chance to be alone with him yet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " well, i'm kinda on a clock here.", "answer": "  oh fonzie.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " undo it. undo it. undo it.", "answer": " fonzie met mork. mork froze fonzie.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " yeah, but umm\u009a yes, but, fonzie was already cool, so he wasn't hurt, right?", "answer": " yeah, that's right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": "  how are you doing?", "answer": " okay, doctor says any minute now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " hey, y'know, alice is gonna be here so soon, you couldn't just like do me a favor and like, like hold them in?", "answer": " sorry frank, i'm kinda in the middle of the last favor you asked me to do.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " rachel.", "answer": " monica, this is dan , one of the guys that we're gonna be going out with on saturday.  uh dan, monica.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " nice to meet you.", "answer": " hello dan! i'm really looking forward to saturday night! really, really!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " so dan, nurse not a doctor huh? kinda girlie isn't it?", "answer": " chandler!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " nah that's okay. i'm just doing this to put myself through medical school.", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " and it didn't feel so girlie during the gulf war.", "answer": " sure.  and listen, thanks for doing that for us, by the way.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " so, why wait 'til saturday, are you free tomorrow?", "answer": " sure! i'll get somebody to cover my shift.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " oh, great!", "answer": "  hey, how 'bout it? you, me, saturday night? delivery room nurse: no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " all right. very good.", "answer": " oo, this is a big one. eww! arghhhh!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " ohh, get these things out of me!", "answer": " breathe! breathe! breathe throw the pain.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " i do too! i do too!", "answer": " argh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " argh!", "answer": " argh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " yeah, i love you. okay, bye!  hi!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " that was alice's mom, she said she left five hours ago. she should be here by now!", "answer": " oh, honey, don\u0092t worry. she's gonna make it on time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " yeah. so frank, three babies. whew, that just seems like a lot, huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": "  not to me.", "answer": " yeah, fair enough.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " bye dan!", "answer": " uh, bye monica.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " all right, i need a clamp, sterile towel, and channel 31.", "answer": " what is that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " oh my god!", "answer": " oh, no-no-no, it's a good one! fonzie plays the bongos. all right, are you ready? it's time to start pushing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " okay, now push! that's it push! just concentrate on pushing! yeah, here we go!", "answer": " i see the head.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " yes, it has a head!", "answer": " all right. keep pushing! come on!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " i can't believe there's somebody coming out of you right now. there's somebody coming out of you! is it? is it? it's my son.", "answer": " all right. here's your first baby.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " yesssss!!!!! we got a baby boy!!", "answer": " yes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " frank jr. jr.!!", "answer": " oh, how does he look? how does he look?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " okay. you ready to push again?", "answer": " i already had a baby. leave me alone.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " come on little chandler, it's time to be born. come on little chandler! come on!", "answer": " all right, he's coming. he's coming!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " chandler's a girl!", "answer": " oh god, kindergarten flashback.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " they musta read the sonogram wrong. 'cause they, 'cause they thought it was a boy, but chandler's a girl! chandler's a girl!", "answer": " okay, keep saying it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": "  am i too late?!", "answer": " no-no ah, everything's okay. everybody's healthy there's 30 fingers and 30 toes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " we have our babies?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " oh my god.", "answer": " you did it, man.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " so, i'll call you tomorrow.", "answer": " great!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " so, are you really gonna go out with that nurse man?", "answer": " well uh, you and i are just goofing around, i thought, why not goof around with him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " y'know, i don't know if you've ever looked up the term goofing around in the dictionary\u009a well, i have, and the technical definition is, two friends who care a lot about each other and have amazing sex and just wanna spend more time together. but if you have this new fangled dictionary that gets you made at me, then we have to, y'know, get you my original dictionary. i am so bad at this.", "answer": " i think you're better than you think you are.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " really? okay, so\u009a", "answer": "  know when to stop.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " y'know, i sensed that i should stop. so we're okay?", "answer": " yeah. all right, i'm gonna go tell dan that it's not gonna happen.  don't do the dance.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " i think you're my favorite.", "answer": " which one do you have?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " i don't care.", "answer": "  hi.  hey, hi! so uh, frank and alice wanted me to tell you that they're still outside making phone calls.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " but umm, i mean, did you talk to them about, y'know\u009a", "answer": " yeah, umm, no honey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " oh. it was a long shot. hey, you guys can i just like have a second alone with the babies.", "answer": " yeah, sure yeah. yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " phoebe, we are so proud of you! you're amazing!", "answer": " i know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " so does it really hurt as bad as they say?", "answer": " yeah. you won't be able to take it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " so uh, now that little chandler turned out to be a girl, what are they gonna name her?", "answer": " they're gonna call her chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " that's kind of a masculine name, don't you think?", "answer": " works on you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}]